NWLB Files 5309
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NWLB Files
1940-1952
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. National War Labor Board (NWLB)
5309
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Minutes, reports, pamphlets, correspondence, press releases.
5596458
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919); United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945)
5596458
- Panel Member Lists, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Round Table Meeting on the War Labor Board: Where It Is and Where It Is Going, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Application for Approval of a Volunteer or Agreed-Upon Wage or Salary Adjustment Blank Form 10, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Instructional Memo, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Directive Order, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Region 2 Minutes, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Furriers Joint Council (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Steelworkers Organizing Committee (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Texting Workers' Union of America (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UAW, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 439, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)